Guide to the David Richmond Gergen Papers, 1964-1999 (bulk 1971-1992) RL.00443
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2000-0415)
  - [No SR, no box title] (Box 50)
    - DG Editorial: 1992 November 9 Media--Bush (Box 50)
    - 26 Pol--Clinton Bad Economy Ahead (Box 50)
    - DG--LAT (Box 50)
    - [Legal-sized material moved to box 41] (Box 50)
    - New World Order (Box 50)
    - Important Letters (Box 50)
    - Elections 1990,1990 November 6 (Box 50)
    - Week-at-a-glance calendars,1987-1990 (Box 50)
    - Comments--Colleagues (Box 50)
  - [No SR, no box title] (cont.) (Box 51)
    - CSIS: Health Care Reform (Box 51)
    - [Phone log] (Box 51)
    - Reading Material (Box 51)
    - Project Synergy (Box 51)
    - The Johnson Foundation Wingspread Conference (Box 51)
    - What Does Society Need from Higher Education?, report (Box 51)
    - [Loose material: CSIS] (Box 51)
    - [Loose material: Mostly notes] (Box 51)
    - David Gergen: reader service (Box 51)
    - Clinton's Economic Package: A New Direction Depicted in Reality (Box 51)
    - TIAA CREF (Box 51)
    - [Loose material: Mostly Press Clippings] (Box 51)
    - Baton Rouge, LA:May 25 (Box 51)
    - Contents of Drawer List (Box 51)
    - DG Phone Logs1992 May 1-1992 July 1 (Box 51)
  - [No SR, no box title] (Box 51)
    - Call Sheets/DG Phone Log:1992 May 1-1992 July 2 (Box 51)
    - Copies: Phone Logs1991 October 1-1992 February 10, 2 folders (Box 51)
    - DG Phone Logs back-up copies1992 February 10-1992 May 30 (Box 51)
    - Phone Logs1992 October 12-1993 January 7 (Box 51)
    - [1 computer disk removed; computer material migrated to server as Disk007, labeled DOS 3.1] (Box 51)
    - 8 notepads with notes (Box 51)
    - [Loose material: Flood relief] (Box 51)
    - [Flood Relief] (Box 51)
    - Flood Response Mobilization and Recovery Briefing and Resource Book, 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Briefing Book for the Trip of the President to Des Moines, Iowa,1993 July 13-1993 July 14 (Box 51)
    - Flood Materials (Box 51)
    - [Loose material: Mostly regarding flood] (Box 51)
    - 2 manila envelopes of material sent to Dianna Pierce (Box 51)
    - Flood Response Mobilization and Recovery Briefing and Resource Book (Box 51)
    - [Legal-sized material moved to box 41] (Box 51)
    - Phone List (Box 51)
    - Final Pages, 1-3 of 5 folders (Box 51)
  - [No SR, no box title] (cont.) (Box 52)
    - Final Pages (Box 52)
    - Jody's copy (Box 52)
  - [No SR, no box title] (Box 52)
    - Int'l FilesClinton Admin.
      - Bipartisan Leadership--DG notes, 2 folders (Box 52)
      - Gingrich--DG Notes (Box 52)
      - Military Brief.--DG Notes (Box 52)
      - E. Europe--DG Notes (Box 52)
      - Foreign Policy--DG Notes (Box 52)
      - Somalia--DG Notes (Box 52)
      - Europe and Russia--DG Notes (Box 52)
      - Yeltsin--DG Notes (Box 52)
      - Russia (Box 52)
      - DG Notes--Russia--MSC Meeting (Box 52)
      - [Bosnia] (Box 52)
      - [Haiti] (Box 52)
      - G-7 Meeting, 3 folders (Box 52)
    - Clinton Admin. Speeches--Gergen
      - SUNY Geneseo (Box 52)
      - UNC Journalism Speech (Box 52)
      - Remarks at Reagan Library (Box 52)
      - Leadership Summit legal-sized folder moved to box 41 (Box 52)
      - DG Speeches--Transcripts (Box 52)
      - Speech Notes (Box 52)
      - [Legal-sized folders moved to box 41] (Box 52)
    - Foster, Vince (Box 52)
    - James Baker (Box 52)
    - Gridiron (Box 52)
    - Whitewater Files,Clinton Administration, D. Gergen, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Beverly (Box 52)
    - 1995-1996 Dialog files from Lisa Halpern, 3 folders (Box 52)
    - Goleman (DG notes) (Box 52)
    - Rosabeth Moss Kanter (Box 52)
    - R. Moss Kanter/World Class (Box 52)
    - Economics (Box 52)
    - Vanden Heuvel/ [The]Nation (Box 52)
    - Bill Kristol/The Standard (Box 52)
    - Kathleen Hall Jamieson (Box 52)
    - Lisa's Health Care (Box 52)
  - Audio-Visual Materials (Box 53)
    - [Loose material: Info. on Videos] (Box 53)
    - Videocassettes
      - The Third Annual Report of the Secretaries of Defense (Box 53)
      - The Fifth Annual Report of the Secretaries of Defense (Box 53)
      - The Sixth Annual Report of the Secretaries of Defense (Box 53)
      - The Eighth Annual Report of the Secretaries of Defense (Box 53)
      - Two Kinds of Changes (Box 53)
      - Tsongas Committee Swim: 30 Spot1991 November 11 (Box 53)
      - Interview with Japan Broadcasting Corp. (1990) (Box 53)
      - Madonna: The Immaculate Collection (Box 53)
      - WNT1993 May 15-1993 May 17, 1993 May 20, 1993 May 22 (ABC News) (Box 53)
      - WNT,1993 May 21 (ABC News) (Box 53)
      - Kerney [?] (Box 53)
      - Larry King Live,Clinton/Gore OCALA, Fl,1992 October 5 (Box 53)
      - Larry King Live,1992 October 7, PresidentBush Intv., San Antonio, TX (Box 53)
      - Coalition for National Health Care Reform Presentation Tape (Box 53)
      - Bush,June 29, Detroit (Box 53)
      - RESN, Republican Neighborhood Meeting,1993 May 3--Highlights 13 minutes (Box 53)
      - Ntl. Dividend Act, 1992 February (Box 53)
      - Demfinecut (Box 53)
      - WETA (Box 53)
      - The Republicans Before and After Reagan, Hosted by David Gergen, 60 minutes (Box 53)
      - Cross of Fire pt. 2 (Box 53)
      - 1990 American Gas Conference1990 October 29-1990 October 31, Tape 2, 60:00, 2 copies (Box 53)
      - Worldnet 1646/Euronet 652, Date:1990 March 26, Guest: Lantos, Rollins, Fahrenkopf,Producer: DJones, Language: English (Box 53)
      - Phil Donahue w/MacNeil-Lehrer (Box 53)
      - Republicans, 56:00,1992 October 16 (Box 53)
      - America's Political Parties (1988) (Box 53)
      - Part 1, The Democrats: A Quarter Century of Change, (57:48) (Box 53)
      - Part 2, The Republicans: Before and After Reagan, (57:50) (Box 53)
      - Music? (Box 53)
      - Museum of Broadcasting, MacNeil/Lehrer Seminar,1989 February 7 (Box 53)
      - Covering the Environment: Front Page or Yesterday's News? (Box 53)
      - U.S. News and World Report, Atlantic Forum, The Environment,1989 November 2 (Box 53)
  - Audio-visual material (cont.) (Box 54)
    - [Unfoldered materials: Papers accompanying videos] (Box 54)
    - Videocassettes (cont.)
      - Bush Section of America's Political Parties: The Republican's--narrated by David Gergen (Box 54)
      - Dads Tape Only (Box 54)
      - M/L Retrospective (Box 54)
      - Halftime (Box 54)
      - The Democrats: A Quarter Century of Change - America's Political Parties Part 1, 2 videos (Box 54)
      - The Republicans: Before and After Reagan (Hosted by Gergen), 2 copies (Box 54)
      - Shea and Assoc/Fred Woods Prod.: Tsongas for President, 3 ads (Box 54)
      - Discovery Channel Invention Show #1 (Box 54)
      - Am I Blue? A Report on the Threat to Excellence at Yale (Box 54)
      - Koch TV Productions, Inc., Citizen Carter (Box 54)
      - The First Annual Berlin Conference of World Leaders (Box 54)
      - Bill Moyer's A World of Ideas (Box 54)
      - A Conversation with the Secretaries of Education (Box 54)
      - Ulysses and Beyond (Box 54)
      - MacNeil/Lehrer Retrospective: Revised Edition (Box 54)
      - [No label: from Veterans' Creed, Inc.] (Box 54)
      - Term Limits1992 (Box 54)
      - EDSAT Institute Luncheon with Governor Wilkinson, re: Satellite Dedicated for Education (Box 54)
      - EDSAT Institute Luncheon with Governor Wilkinson, re: Satellite Dedicated for Education (Box 54)
      - M/L Retro: Draft Edit. Pt. 1 (Box 54)
      - Tomorrow's Air Force: Reshaping the Future--CSAF (Box 54)
      - A Public Voice--3 Roll-ins (Box 54)
      - Tsongas for President, Shea/Woods Productions, 8 ads (Box 54)
      - RichardNixon Reflects (Box 54)
      - See How They Run (Box 54)
      - Tsongas Committee, Taking Control (Box 54)
      - Tsongas for President, Shea Woods,Alone (Box 54)
  - Audio-Visual Materials (cont.) (Box 55)
    - Videocassettes (cont.)
      - Citizens Jury: Pennsylvania Citizens Jury (Box 55)
      - Citizens Jury: [Unlabeled] (Box 55)
      - Critical Condition: Solving America's Health Care Crisis (Box 55)
      - World in Focus, Council on Foreign Relations (Box 55)
      - V.A. Health Care Crisis (Off Air News Clips) (Box 55)
      - American Citizen's Television,1990 September 29--Education Choice, Guest Host: Pete du Pont (Box 55)
      - CNN News Aircheck--Interview (Box 55)
      - Article 99 (Box 55)
      - Working for America: Business, The Military and the New Workforce (Box 55)
      - Videos from box 51:
        - Dad's Tape, 3 videocassettes (Box 55)
        - America's Political Parties, Part II, The Republicans: Before and After Reagan, Show #102 (Box 55)
        - The Soviets at the Crossroads: PBS Programmers Hi-Lite Tape (Box 55)
        - [No label] (Box 55)
        - Mom's Press Secy, Live at Five,1989 September 19 (Box 55)
        - American Leaders Assess U.S.-Japan Relations (Box 55)
      - [Untitled: video removed from box 48] (Box 55)
    - Audiocassettes
      - Mark Shields (Box 55)
      - WMAL am 630: David Gergen1993 March 1 (Box 55)
      - The Talk Show (1991 October 24) (Box 55)
      - Two Stories Using Sound from David Gergen--WCJW (Box 55)
      - 1991 January 29Morning DuPont Panel, Tapes 1 and 2 (Box 55)
      - David Gergen, Rainbow Room,1993 March 30 [from box 47] (Box 55)
      - TV on the Front Lines: Covering the Middle East, 2 copies (Box 55)
      - A Look at the Nineties, 2 copies (Box 55)
      - Kenneth Duberstein and Mike Berman1991 January 30 (Box 55)
      - Dianne's Promises (Box 55)
      - National Public Radio: ME 900724, Stamberg--Hatch--Metzenbaum (Box 55)
      - Insider Information on the Election (Box 55)
      - Experts DissectBush-Gorbachev Summit (Box 55)
      - Michael Dalby and George Wilson Soundbites (Box 55)
      - America and the World:
        - A Conversation with Stanley Hoffman on American Foreign Policy in a World Transformed,1990 October 18 (Box 55)
        - A Conversation with Cl. Trevor N. Dupuy....[on the Gulf Crisis],1991 January 17 (Box 55)
      - Material removed from box 48 [some Perot transcripts are located in that box]:
        - Ross Perot Phone Interview1992 June 16 (Box 55)
        - Nixon,1992 June 15, Mort and Dave (Box 55)
        - Tape, Notes, Little Rock (Box 55)
        - 1992 May 15: Sen. Moynihan (Box 55)
        - Dave Gergen: Lester Thurow interview (Box 55)
        - Ross Perot Intervu,1992 June 11, 5 tapes (Box 55)
        - Drucker Parts 1 and 2, microcassette (Box 55)
  - Miscellaneous (from plastic box) (Box 55)
    - Business Cards (Box 55)
    - Seashells (in microfilm box) (Box 55)
    - Cross Pens (Box 55)